(Howard:)Hey, I didn't see
you giving back
(Howard:)your Snoopy
snow cone maker.
(Raj:)That was all a lie?
(Raj:)This year's gifts
are already wrapped.
(Howard:)And as long as we're talking
about betraying our friends,
(Howard:)how about the month Sheldon
spent grinding up insects
(Howard:)and mixing them
into Leonard's food?
(Sheldon:)Well, excuse me.
(Sheldon:)That was not a betrayal.
(Sheldon:)That was an experiment
to determine
(Sheldon:)at what concentration
food starts tasting "mothy."
You put moths in my food?!
(Sheldon:)For science.
(Raj:)I can't believe you kissed
my sister with moth mouth.
Well, I can't believe you
used Sheldon's toothbrush.
(Sheldon:)You used my toothbrush?
(Raj:)Not the brush part,
just the little rubber thing
(Raj:)to pick food from my teeth
and massage my gums.
Okay, I-I think
it's safe to say
(Leonard:)that we've all done
some things
(Leonard:)we're not
particularly proud of.
(Leonard:)But come on,
we're friends.